Inauguration 2009 Sermons and Orations Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Submissions, 2008-2009
  - La Canada Congregational Church (La Canada, California)
    - Say it Again, Sam! 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: CD [missing]; afc2009001_0151_sr01 (Box 11)
  - Unitarian Universalist Fellowship of Boca Raton (Boca Raton, Florida)
    - One by One: Justice, Equity and Compassion in Human Relations, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/132)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 4/132)
  - First Church Unitarian (Littleton, Massachusetts)
    - Now We Must, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/133)
    - Program, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 4/133)
    - Now We Must, 2009-01-25, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0153_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Congregational Church of South Hempstead, United Church of Christ (South Hempstead, New York)
    - Program, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 4/134)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-25, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0154_sr01 (Box 11)
  - Christ Lutheran Church (Germantown, Maryland)
    - Lessons From a Busy Week, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/135)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 4/135)
    - The Kingdom of God is at Hand, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/135)
    - Program, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 4/135)
    - Sermons, 2009-01-18 and 2009-01-25, 1 sound recording: digital wma file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0155_sr01 (Box 11)
  - Harry S. Wright, Minister of Shiloh Baptist Church (Bennettsville, South Carolina)
    - "What inauguration of Barack Obama means," Marlboro Herald-Advocate, 1 newspaper clipping; afc2009001_0156_ms01 (Box-folder 4/136)
  - First Christian Church (Mount Vernon, Washington)
    - Whose Dream Is It? 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/137)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 4/137)
    - Business card (Box-folder 4/137)
  - Adath Israel Congregation (Lawrenceville, New Jersey)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-16, 1 sound recording: digital mp3 and wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0158_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Yale Avenue Christian Church (Tulsa, Oklahoma)
    - Dear Mr. President, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/138)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 4/138)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: CD [missing]; afc2009001_0159_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Alpharetta Presbyterian Church (Alpharetta, Georgia)
    - Inaugurating Disciples, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/139)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 4/139)
    - Business card (Box-folder 4/139)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital mp3 and wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0160_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Antioch Baptist Church North (Atlanta, Georgia)
    - Three Miracles, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/140)
    - Who He Is, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/140)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 4/140)
    - Three Miracles, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0161_sr01 (Box 12)
    - Who He Is, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0161_sr02 (Box 12)
    - Who He Is, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0161_mv01 (Box 8)
    - Three Miracles, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0161_mv02 (Box 8)
  - Wheat Street Baptist Church (Atlanta, Georgia)
    - The 'Yes-We-Can' Theology and Celebration Time, Pray On! 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0162_mv01 (Box 8)
  - United Centers for Spiritual Living (Golden, Colorado)
    - Business card (Box-folder 4/141)
    - Celebrate Your Life, 2009-01-22, 3 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0163_sr01-sr03 (Box 12)
  - Broadway Baptist Church (Fort Worth, Texas)
    - An Unlikely Prophet, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/142)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 4/142)
    - An Unlikely Prophet, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0164_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Central Wesleyan Church hosting Elwood, Indiana, Ministerial Association (Elwood, Indiana)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: VHS; afc2009001_0165_mv01
  - United Methodist Church of Spring Valley (Spring Valley, New York)
    - The Challenge of Faith, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/143)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 4/143)
    - The Challenge of Faith, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0166_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Saint Peter Missionary Baptist Church (Atlanta, Georgia)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 4/144)
    - Pastor Eric Vincent Thomas biographical sketch, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 4/144)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0167_sr01 (Box 12)
  - St. Luke's Episcopal Church (Washington D.C.)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0168_ms01.doc (Box-folder 4/145)
    - Inauguration Day Homily, 2009-01-20, 1 digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0168_ms02.doc (Box-folder 4/145)
  - Allen Avenue Unitarian Universalist Church (Portland, Maine)
    - Growth is Life, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon: digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0169_ms01.doc (Box-folder 4/146)
  - Insight Atlanta (Atlanta, Georgia)
    - Obama, the Dharma, and America Near the Eve of the Inauguration of President Barack Hussein Obama, 2009-01-14, 1 sermon: digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0170_ms01.doc (Box-folder 4/147)
  - Congregation Beth El (South Orange, New Jersey)
    - King, Heschel, Obama & YOU! 2009-01-17, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/148)
    - King, Heschel, Obama & YOU! 2009-01-17, 1 sound recording: digital mp3and wave files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0171_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Beth Shalom Congregation (Columbia, Maryland)
    - The Top Ten Leadership Lessons from Exodus, 2009-01-16, 1 sermon: digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0172_ms01.doc (Box-folder 4/149)
    - Is Seeing Believing? The Power of Faith, 2009-01-16, 1 sermon: digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0172_ms02.doc (Box-folder 4/149)
    - Introductory Remarks, 2009-01-16, 1 digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0172_ms03.doc (Box-folder 4/149)
    - Introduction of Speaker Rev. Dr. John Lewis Wright of First Baptist Church of Gilford, Maryland, 2009-01-16, 1 digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0172_ms04.doc (Box-folder 4/149)
    - Comments by Rabbi Susan Grossman, 2009-01-16, 1 digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0172_ms05.doc (Box-folder 4/149)
    - Program, 1 digital pub file and printed copy; afc2009001_0172_ms06.pub (Box-folder 4/149)
  - Hindu Temple of Metropolitan Washington (Adelphi, Maryland)
    - Introduction letter, 3 poems and 3 photographs, 2009-01-20, 1 digital pdf file and printed copy; afc2009001_0173_ms01.pdf (Box-folder 4/150)
    - Photographs of service, 2009-01-20, 19 photographs: digital, color, jpg files; afc2009001_0173_ph01-ph19.jpg (Box-folder 4/150)
    - Greetings from Indian Community, 2 Hindu Temple, For Our Beloved President Barack Obama, 2009-01-19 and 2009-01-20, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0173_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Johnson Ferry Baptist Church (Marietta, Georgia)
    - A Dream Realized, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0174_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Mt. Zion Baptist Church (LaFayette, Georgia)
    - The In-Crowd, 2009-01-25, 3 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0175_sr01-sr03 (Box 12)
  - Laguna Niguel Presbyterian Church (Laguna Niguel, California)
    - Walking in the Light: It Is All About You, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0176_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Mt. Sinai Baptist Church (Whistler, Alabama)
    - Amazing Faith, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/151)
    - Handwritten note (Box-folder 4/151)
    - Amazing Faith, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: DVD [faulty disc]; afc2009001_0177_mv01 (Box 17)
  - Waters United Methodist Church (Oxford, Maryland)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 4/152)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0178_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Light of the World Christian Church (Indianapolis, Indianapolis)
    - Barack, Hallelujah! 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/153)
    - Barack, Hallelujah! 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0179_sr01 (Box 12)
  - American Atheists (Cranford, New Jersey)
    - Obama Oration, 2009-01-25, 1 sound recording: MiniDV; afc2009001_0180_mv01
  - Florida Ave Baptist Church (Washington, D.C.)
    - Don't You Know God is Able, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/154)
    - Biographical sketch of The Reverend Dr. James D. Peters, Jr (Box-folder 4/154)
    - "Denver's Rev. Peters Reflects on MLK," cbs4denver.com, 2009-01-18 and "MLK Day 2009: One Step closer to the 'dream,'" The Rocky Mountain News, 2009-01-19, 2 news articles (Box-folder 4/154)
    - Political flyer, 2008-08 (Box-folder 4/154)
    - Don't You Know God is Able, 2009-01-18, 1 CD cover (Box-folder 4/154)
    - Photograph of Reverend Dr. James D. Peters, Jr., 1 photographic print: color, 2 x 3 in.; afc2009001_0181_ph01 (Box-folder 4/154)
    - Don't You Know God is Able, 2009-01-18, 9 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0181_sr01-sr09 (Box 12)
  - Germantown Mennonite Church (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Talk at Germantown Mennonite Church, 2009-01-18, 1 digital rtf file and printed copy; afc2009001_0182_ms01.rtf (Box-folder 4/155)
    - Program, 2009-01-18, 1 digital pdf file and printed copy; afc2009001_0182_ms02.pdf (Box-folder 4/155)
    - Talk at Germantown Mennonite Church, 2009-01-18, 2 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0182_sr01-sr02 (Box 12)
  - New Philadelphia African Methodist Episcopal Church (Rancho Dominguez, California)
    - Ruth 2:1-10, Let's Just Kiss and Say Good-Bye, Pt. III, 2009-01-18, 2 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0183_sr01-sr02 (Box 12)
  - Universalist Church (West Hartford, Connecticut)
    - An Open Letter to President-Elect Barack Obama, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 4/156)
    - Call to the White House, 2009-01-18, 1 speech (Box-folder 4/156)
    - Jan K. Nielsen and Sarah K. Person, preaching, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: audio cassette tape; afc2009001_0184_sr01 (Box 12)
  - New Life Anointed Ministries International (Woodbridge, Virginia)
    - Hope the Anchor of Your Soul, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0185_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Love Life Christian Fellowship (Ellenwood, Georgia)
    - For a People with a Mind to Work, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/157)
    - Program, 2009-01-25
    - For a People with a Mind to Work, 2009-01-25, 4 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0186_sr01-sr04 (Box 12)
  - Village Church of Westwood Lutheran (Los Angeles, California)
    - Inauguration Sermon, 2009-01-11 (Box-folder 4/158)
  - Greater Travelers Rest Baptist Church (Decatur, Georgia)
    - Race Still Matters, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/159)
    - Race Still Matters, 2009-01-25, 4 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0188_sr01-sr04 (Box 12)
    - Race Still Matters, 2009-01-25, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0188_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Olive Branch Interfaith Peace Partnership (Nyack, New York)
    - Program, 2009-01-19 (Box-folder 4/160)
    - Rebirthing King Rebirthing America, 2009-01-19, 3 sound recordings: audio cassette tapes; afc2009001_0189_sr01-sr03
  - Third Street Church of God (Washington, D.C.)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 4/161)
    - Witnesses of History and Hope, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0190_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Our Lady Star of the Sea (New Orleans, Louisiana) and St. James the Apostle Church (Las Vegas, Nevada)
    - The Election of President Barack, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/162)
    - "The Election of President Barack," recorded at St. James the Apostle Church, 2009-01-25, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0191_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Apostolic Faith Church of God of Washington, D.C. (Washington, D.C.)
    - Yes I Can! 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/163)
    - Program, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 4/163)
    - Book flyer, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 4/163)
    - Photographs of congregation, 2009-01-25, 5 photographic prints: color, 4 x 6 in.; afc2009001_0192_ph01-ph05 (Box-folder 4/163)
  - Emmanuel Church in the City of Boston (Boston, Massachusetts)
    - Reflections on the Inauguration of Barack Obama as President of the United States, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon: digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0193_ms01.doc
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 4/164)
    - Reflections on the Inauguration of Barack Obama as President of the United States, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0193_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Grace Cathedral (San Francisco, California)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 4/165)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 4/165)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0194_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Boston Jewish Spirit (Boston, Massachusetts)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-16, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0195_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Vivekananda Vedanta Society of Chicago (Chicago, Illinois)
    - Message of Swami Vivekananda, 2009-01-22 and 2009-01-26, 1 sound recording; afc2009001_0196_sr01 (Box 12)
  - All Dulles Area Muslim Society (Sterling, Virginia)
    - The Promise of President Obama, 2009-01-23, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/166)
    - The Promise of President Obama, 2009-01-23, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0197_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Mount Zion United Methodist Church (Hamilton, Virginia)
    - Morning Services, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: audio cassette tape; afc2009001_0198_sr01
    - Morning Services, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: VHS; afc2009001_0198_mv01
  - Bethlehem Baptist Church (Edgefield, South Carolina)
    - Letter, 2009-02-09 (Box-folder 4/167)
  - Temple Emanuel (Beverly Hills, California)
    - A Prayer for Our Country, 2009-01-23, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/168)
  - St. James Christian Methodist Episcopal Church (Columbus, Georgia)
    - The Audacity to Dream, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 5/169)
    - The Audacity to Dream, 2009-01-18, 13 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0201_sr01-sr13 (Box 12)
  - University Christian Church (San Diego, California)
    - Celebrating Barack Obama...and Rick Warren, Too, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 5/170)
    - Celebrating Barack Obama...and Rick Warren, Too, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0202_mv01 (Box 8)
    - Celebrating Barack Obama...and Rick Warren, Too, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: audio cassette tape; afc2009001_0202_sr01
  - St. John Progressive Missionary Baptist Church (Tampa, Florida)
    - Program, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 5/171)
    - Dare to Be a Dreamer, 2009-01-18, 7 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0203_sr01-sr07 (Box 12)
    - There is Power in his Name, 2009-01-25, 5 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0203_sr08-sr12 (Box 12)
    - There is Power in his Name, 2009-01-25, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0203_mv01 (Box 8)
    - Dare to Be a Dreamer, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0203_mv02 (Box 8)
  - Centenary United Methodist Church (Winston-Salem, North Carolina)
    - Lighten Our Darkness: The Call to Discipleship and the Audacity of Hope, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 5/172)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 5/172)
    - Biographical sketch of Dr. Peter Graves, 2009-02-20 (Box-folder 5/172)
    - Photograph of Dr. Peter Graves, 2009-01-18, 1 photograph: color, digital image printout; afc2009001_0204_ph01 (Box-folder 5/172)
    - Lighten Our Darkness: The Call to Discipleship and the Audacity of Hope, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0204_sr01 (Box 12)
  - ORS Multimidia Interativa Ltda. (Salvador, Brazil)
    - Letter to U. S. Consulate General, 2009-07-08 (Box-folder 7/256)
    - We Are All Americans/ Somos Todos Brasileiros, 2009-01-20, Song lyrics (Box-folder 7/256)
    - Obama Inauguration - Posse de Obama interviews and music performance, 2009-01-20, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0205_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Lindsay Street Baptist Church (Atlanta, Georgia)
    - The Prisoner and the Politician, 1 sermon: digital doc file and printed copy (Box-folder 5/173)
  - Unitarian Universalist Church of Palo Alto (Palo Alto, California)
    - Now Our Children Can Fly, 2009-01-11, 1 sermon: digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0207_ms01.doc (Box-folder 5/174)
    - Now Our Children Can Fly, 2009-01-11, 1 sound recording: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0207_sr01-sr02
  - Oakhurst Presbyterian Church (Decatur, Georgia)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 5/175)
    - The Content of Our Character, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital mp3 file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0208_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Lovely Valley Baptist Church (Wirtz, Virginia)
    - Program and sermon, "I Am Sending You", 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 5/176)
  - Red Oak Grove Baptist Church (Modoc, South Carolina)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav and mp3 files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0210_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Unitarian Universalist Church of Lexington (Lexington, Kentucky)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-25, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0211_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Unitarian Universalist Congregation of Danbury (Danbury, Connecticut)
    - Cautious Optimism, Wild Hope, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 5/177)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 5/177)
  - Manchester United Methodist Church (Manchester, Missouri)
    - Some Sweet Day, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 5/178)
    - Some Sweet Day, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0213_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Mt. Level Missionary Baptist Church (Durham, North Carolina)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 5/179)
  - Culmore United Methodist Church (Falls Church, Virginia) and The Residences at Thomas Circle (Washington, D.C.)
    - What do You See, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon
    - Culmore United Methodist program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 5/180)
    - The Residences at Thomas Circle program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 5/180)
    - Photograph of Rev. Dr. Youtha Hardman Cromwell, 2009-01-18, 1 photographic print: color, 2 x 3 in.; afc2009001_0215_ph01 (Box-folder 5/180)
  - Temple Hillel B'nai Torah (West Roxbury, Massachusetts)
    - What the Inauguration of Barack Obama Means to Me, 2009-01-17, 1 sermon (Box-folder 5/181)
    - What the Inauguration of Barack Obama Means to Me, 2009-01-17, 2 video recordings: digital files submitted on 2 DVDs; afc2009001_0216_mv01-mv02 (Box 8)
  - Center in the Park (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Letter (Box-folder 5/182)
    - Official Barack Obama Presidential Inauguration Event, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0217_mv01 (Box 8)
  - First Presbyterian Church (Hamilton, New Jersey)
    - Meeting Jesus Changes Everything, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 5/183)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 5/183)
    - Meeting Jesus Changes Everything, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0218_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Kittamaqundi Community Church (Columbia, Maryland)
    - Letters to President Obama, 2009-01-25, 23 letters (Box-folder 5/184)
    - Heather's Sharing and Response, 2009-01-25, 2 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0219_sr01-sr02 (Box 12)
  - Dublin Community Church, (Dublin, New Hampshire)
    - Come and See, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon: digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0220_ms01.doc (Box-folder 5/185)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 5/185)
    - Come and See, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0220_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Butler Street Christian Methodist Episcopal Church (Atlanta, Georgia)
    - Here Comes that Dreamer, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 5/186)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 5/186)
    - DVD cover (Box-folder 5/186)
    - Here Comes that Dreamer, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0221_mv01 (Box 8)
  - First Unitarian Society (Minneapolis, Minnesota)
    - Seven Principles for President Obama, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon: digital pdf file and printed copy; afc2009001_0222_ms01.pdf (Box-folder 5/187)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 5/187)
    - Program draft, 2009-01-18, 1 digital pdf file and printed copy; afc2009001_0222_ms03.pdf (Box-folder 5/187)
    - Seven Principles for President Obama, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital mp3 and wav files submitted on CDs; afc2009001_0222_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Goodloe Memorial Unitarian Universalist Congregation (Bowie, Maryland)
    - Leadership and Keeping Oaths, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 5/188)
    - Leadership and Keeping Oaths, 2009-01-25, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0223_mv01 (Box 8)
  - St. Paul Baptist Church (Oxnard, California)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 5/189)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0224_mv01 (Box 8)
  - St. Mary's Church (Rochester, New York)
    - Priest, Prophet and King, 2009-01-17 and 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 5/190)
  - First Unitarian Society of Madison, Wisconsin (Madison, Wisconsin)
    - An Inauguration of Hope?, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0226_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Episcopal Church of the Holy Advent (Clinton, Connecticut)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 5/191)
  - Unity Palo Alto Community Church (Palo Alto, California)
    - Daily Word, 2009-01-18, 1 flyer: digital pdf file and printed copy; afc2009001_0228_ms01.pdf (Box-folder 5/192)
    - Program, 2009-01-18, 1 digital pdf file and printed copy; afc2009001_0228_ms02.pdf (Box-folder 5/192)
    - Church Principles, 2009-01-18, 1 flyer: digital pdf file and printed copy; afc2009001_0228_ms03.pdf (Box-folder 5/192)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0228_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Neighborhood Unitarian Universalist Church (Pasadena, California)
    - Dear Mr. President, 2009-02-01, 1 sermon (Box-folder 5/193)
    - Dear Mr. President, 2009-02-01, 3 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0229_sr01-sr03 (Box 12)
    - One is Silver and the Other is Gold, 2009-02-08, 1 sermon (Box-folder 5/194)
    - One is Silver and the Other is Gold, 2009-02-08, 3 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0230_sr01-sr03 (Box 12)
  - First Presbyterian Church (Holland, Michigan)
    - Scapegoats and Rescue Dogs, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 5/195)
    - Scapegoats and Rescue Dogs, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital mp3 file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0231_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Central Presbyterian Church (Lexington, Kentucky)
    - God's Dream, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 5/196)
    - Hymn booklet, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 5/196)
    - God's Dream, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0232_sr01 (Box 12)
  - Rev. Anthony Walker (Spencer, Oklahoma)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: Hi 8 tape; afc2009001_0233_mv01
  - Church of Saint Ann (Lawrenceville, New Jersey)
    - Homily- The Present Opportunity, 2008-11-16 (Box-folder 5/197)
  - First Presbyterian Church (Ann Arbor, Michigan)